[Taiki sighs]
Why does Kyo gotta say weird stuff?
The one I have a crush on is Chinatsu--
[groans, spits coffee]
[coughs]
Chinatsu, what are you doing here?
You're in my house?
My grandpa's doing well after his surgery.
So I'll be staying here again
starting tomorrow.
I came to bring some stuff.
[Taiki] I guess I knew
she was coming back soon.
Thanks again for taking me in, Taiki.
Uh, you're welcome.
But tonight,
I'll be sleeping over at Karen's.
You two are close.
Well, we have known each other
since kindergarten.
[Taiki] She's acting totally normal.
Was she completely unfazed
by what happened during the play?
Or maybe she didn't actually come see it.
But if that were true, she probably
would've told me she couldn't make it.
[grunts]
[door opens]
[groans] What a fiasco.
On our way back from shopping,
we were eating popcorn,
and then Chii's mom spilled it
all over the place at our front door.
[groans] Trash bags...
where are the trash bags?
Why don't I help you clean it up?
[Yukiko] If you don't mind.
[Taiki] Chinatsu!
Um... about the play
at the Cultural Festival--
[grunts]
[laughs]
Aren't those so good?
[grunts]
[Taiki] That is beside the point!
I wanted to talk about the rumors.
About the kiss,
and if Hina and I are dating...
[gulps]
Even if it isn't bothering Chinatsu...
I still want to talk to her about it.
[opening theme song playing]
BLUE BOX
EPISODE 21
A CHANCE TO BLOSSOM
[bell chiming]
Taiki, I've got your back.
Huh?
[Nishida] Don't you worry.
I know everything.
I know that you didn't kiss Hina,
and that the rumors about you two dating
are a complete lie.
The rumors are false, aren't they?
[Taiki] Yes, they are,
but could you let up a little?
[crying] Just don't you go
and betray me like Haryu did.
Nishida's secret crush
went to his booth to get her fortune read,
and asked for his help with her crush
on a guy from the track and field club.
Dang.
Anyway, I'm relieved.
I'm glad you didn't get hurt.
That was scary when the confetti ball
fell from outta nowhere.
You saw the play, then?
I am your captain after all.
I was there with Haryu, his girlfriend,
and Kano from the girls' basketball team.
[gasps]
[Taiki] What do you know,
I was right. She was there!
Even the second and third-years
are gossiping about it.
[scoffs] Not really a surprise though.
The rhythmic gymnastics girl is famous.
Anyone who was there
knows it was an accident,
but rumors like that
often take on a life of their own.
So make sure you look out for her.
[grunts softly]
[grunts]
The thirst tax, 12,000 yen.
Wait, you raised the price again?
No, I didn't.
It's 'cause there's two of you.
Wait, me?
I'm just messing with you!
[girl] Hina!
Mm? Yeah!
On second thought,
she'd never go out with you.
[Taiki groans]
If anyone's talking smack about you,
I'll smack them right back.
Thanks so much, Captain.
[girl] It's them, isn't it?
The ones supposedly dating?
Well, I heard it wasn't true.
Oh. Seriously?
A lot of weird rumors going around.
Are you okay?
You are living with him again, right?
[groans]
Did you see that just now?
That was a Steph Curry shot!
[Nagisa] Well,
the point of living with him
is so she can keep playing basketball.
One more.
[Nagisa] I guess Chinatsu just
isn't interested in that kind of gossip.
[Karen] Still,
it's been forever, hasn't it?
You coming to stay over, I mean.
You slept over a lot when we were kids.
I've been so tied up with practice lately.
Geez. Everybody's all,
"Practice, practice."
Well, you have your work, too, right?
I mean, I do, but...
Kengo will be busy
with practice for a while,
which means he'll be a little distant.
And I won't hear from him. [sighs]
You say that,
but wouldn't you be mad at him
if he prioritized you over his club?
Obviously, I would!
I would never want him
to use me as an excuse.
If I'm being honest,
it's when he's playing badminton
that I hear myself think,
"Gosh, he's just so cool."
[Chinatsu sighs]
And that's why,
you'll fill my attention fix!
You're lucky to have me. [giggles]
I'm cheating on him with you! [giggles]
I really do have to keep pesky bugs
away from you, bestie.
Not bugs.
I'm only bringing this up
'cause they asked me to, okay?
A guy friend of mine
from a different school
asked me to introduce you to him.
He would like to know
if he can get your number.
No, thank you.
That was decisive!
I've never been very good
at talking to people I don't know.
You really don't have
any interest in romance, huh?
[girl 1] I'm gonna marry teacher
when I grow up!
[girl 2] Me, too!
[Karen] Back in kindergarten,
you were the only one
who was unaffected by Mr. Nakamura.
Everyone was just acting grown-up.
But you may have a point.
I'm not as good
with this stuff as other people.
Could it be, Chii,
that there's someone you like?
[Chinatsu groans]
[Karen] What's up
with this bleak look on her face?
Mm-hm. There is...
someone I like.
[soft music playing]
Is there any chance that it's...
Inomata?
Mm.
So, you're in love with him.
I don't know that I'm there yet!
Huh? You're not sure how you feel?
Hmm... How can I explain it...
Okay, so it's like I'm growing a flower.
[Karen] Here we go again
with her weird metaphors.
When I say that I like him,
I mean that my feelings
have only started to sprout.
When I'd see him at morning practice,
I just thought of him
as the guy who was always there.
But once I started talking to him,
and got to know him better,
I started feeling attracted to him,
and the sprout began to grow.
The more I catch myself
being attracted to him...
the bigger the seedling gets.
But then I go...
get tied up playing basketball,
or life gets in the way.
So the flower hasn't had
a chance to blossom yet.
So "blossoming" would be falling in love.
On top of that, there was what happened
during the play the other day.
I don't know, it took me by surprise.
Well, listen, I'm not the kind of person
who falls in love easily, either.
So I understand how you feel.
But all this buzz
about whether they kissed or not...
It was an accident, so it doesn't matter.
I would be out the minute
rumors started spreading around.
I would've snapped the seedling off
if I were you.
But I think if you'd ask other people...
some would describe your
"sprouting" feelings as "falling in love."
But that's because everyone's different,
not because there's one correct answer
when it comes to love.
Honestly, with romance,
everyone goes at their own speed.
You aren't the type of person
to go and date someone
just because you want a boyfriend,
and I think that you tend to tread
very cautiously when it comes to dating.
So I guess I understand
why you might not be totally sure
that you're in love with Inomata.
[Chinatsu sighs]
But while you're busy
thinking about it this way,
someone else may come along
and snatch him away from you.
You don't have to be mean like that.
It's just how things work.
Look, all that I'm trying
to get across to you, Chii...
is that I want you to have
a great love story of your own.
[Chinatsu exclaims]
[Karen] There's no predicting
when it'll happen.
But when the time comes,
and you realize you do love someone...
I want to make sure
that you accept your own feelings.
[Chinatsu] Mm.
[Karen] There are some people
who would say she's already in love.
But if I had to guess...
Chinatsu probably feels like
she's missing one last piece.
My younger sister could stand to learn
a thing or two from you.
Why's that?
She changes her boyfriends like underwear.
Once, she told me she broke up
with someone 'cause he walked too fast--
[Ayame] Sissy!
I need your nail polish remover.
[Karen] Speak of the devil.
I gave it to you the other day, Ayame.
What?
No, you did not. [gasps]
Oh! Hi!
Chii!
Your hair's silky as always.
And you have such beautiful skin!
Must be how active you are!
But you hate exercise, right?
What I hate is getting all sweaty.
By the way, Ayame,
didn't you have a date
with your boyfriend today?
I broke up with him.
What, again?
Yeah, again.
Whenever we went to a café,
they'd always ask him to repeat his order!
Like, get it together, and enunciate!
But who cares about him!
I've already moved on to my next crush.
[Chinatsu gasps]
Chii, you mustn't live by her example.
[Ayame] What are you talking about?
[Karen] About how you completely
have your head in the clouds.
[Chinatsu] What was it that
got you interested in him?
[Ayame] What? Oh, he's hot.
INOMATA
[door sliding]
Thank you again for taking me in.
[all] Welcome back, Chinatsu!
[Yukiko] Oh, I really missed you!
At this point,
it's like you're my own child!
[Taiki's grandfather]
Well, come on in, come on in.
We'll go and get the rest of your things.
Why don't we have sushi
like the first day she was here?
[grunts softly]
[sighs]
Make way. Cargo is coming through!
I'll take it up.
[Yukiko] You will?
[Taiki] As usual,
I can't really tell
what's going through her head.
[sighs softly]
[Hina] Taiki.
I've got a club budget form.
An upperclassman said you needed one.
Thanks.
What happened, did your net snap?
"Strings" not "net."
Yeesh.
You enjoy people's mistakes, huh?
To think you're such a butthead.
I wasn't making fun of you!
Don't you see how they act together?
It seems like
the rumors are true after all.
[girl] No way.
[Taiki grunts]
Don't let it get under your skin.
For my part, I've figured out how to use
those rumors to my advantage.
Use them?
"Oh, it's up to Taiki."
"He can make the rumors
real any time he likes."
What?
O-ho, it's working!
[laughs]
The groundwork's all but been laid!
I'll stick with this strategy
for the time being!
[Taiki] I was worrying over nothing.
[sighs]
Well, I guess that's her own way
of being considerate.
[Kyo] Hmm.
[Taiki] Don't even start.
I wasn't gonna.
[Coach Yuasa] Everybody, gather up!
[boys] Okay!
[footsteps]
So, I believe I had each of you write down
your goals at the start of the term.
[Taiki] There are a lot of things
I need to think about.
- [Coach Yuasa continues indistinctly]
- But now that the festival's over,
I need to give my full focus
back to practice.
I have to get good enough
to beat Yusa again.
Moving right along, today,
we have a new member joining.
- Really?
- [all murmuring]
[Coach Yuasa] Although,
they won't be joining as a player.
Hi, guys!
I'm Ayame Moriya. I'll be your manager!
- [boys gasp]
- What?
But she's so cute.
Our club finally has a girl manager!
- All right!
- This rules!
[all cheering]
Hey, wait. Where's the guy
with the bowl cut?
[boy 1] Huh?
[Ayame] I saw him in this gym
about two weeks ago.
He's super hot, and exactly my type!
Lean but muscular,
cool vibe, and a bowl cut.
[boy 2] Oh,
maybe she's talking about Yusa?
[boy 3] He's a student over at Sajikawa.
He was only here
to play in a practice match.
What? Oh, then I won't be able
to see him every day?
[boy 2] He doesn't even go here.
[Ayame] So I don't get the chance
to wash his uniform?
[boy 3] That's a little sus.
Okay, well, nice knowing you!
- Bye--
- [Haryu] Not so fast!
Kengo.
It's exactly as Karen said.
She knew something was up
when you wanted to do this.
[crying] What other choice did I have?
He matches my type
in the looks department!
I just wanna see that beautiful face
of his and get all blushy!
[boy] Haryu, do you know her?
[Haryu] Girlfriend's little sis.
[Taiki] Oh, she's Karen's sister!
[boy 1] I bet we'll have practice matches
with them again, though. So...
[boy 3] She'll probably see him
at tournaments.
[boy 1] I mean, yeah, this might be
the best way for her to meet him.
Just kidding. You'll be dealing
with me after all.
[boys] She's a real strategist.
All right then, Taiki.
Show our new manager the ropes.
Yes, sir.
[Taiki] This is the storage room.
This is where you mix up
the sports drinks.
And this right here...
is our locker room.
[groans]
Yeah, I know it's a little messy.
A little?
Does no one clean in here?
It stinks!
I honestly can't believe it.
[groans]
[Taiki] She has no trouble
saying what's on her mind.
Haryu said she's Karen's sister.
She doesn't seem like
a bad person, but uh...
[Ayame gasps, shrieks]
There's a spider! Spider!
[Taiki] She's so close to me!
[Ayame grunting]
[grunts]
Oh, Chii!! You have to help me!
[Taiki] She's making it sound
like I did something!
- [crying] There's a spider.
- Inomata, what'd you do?
I didn't do anything!
We just found a spider, and...
[screams] It's coming this way!
- Hurry up and make it go away!
- Don't push me!
- I need a tissue!
- Use your bare hands!
[Chinatsu exclaims softly]
Wow, Chii, my hero!
[Taiki] Huh? I thought that Chinatsu
was afraid of bugs.
[Chinatsu] See, that wasn't so bad.
[Taiki] I guess she got over it.
So, what is it that you're doing
in the boys' badminton locker room?
Somehow or other,
I got roped into being their manager.
[Taiki] Come on! You wanted this job.
Their manager?
So this guy's been teaching me
how to do the job.
Oh, I'm "this guy"?
Oh, right, you have a name, what was it?
Taiki Inomata.
Yeah. "Inota" then.
Huh?
[Ayame] Come on, Inota! We've gotta grab
some trash bags and clean up this pigsty!
[Taiki] Don't call me like I'm your pet!
[door creaks, closes]
[lock clicks]
Okay, well, see you later, Chii!
[gasps softly]
We're gonna need
some rubber gloves for this.
When it comes to romance,
everyone goes at their own speed.
[Chinatsu] That's what she meant.
EIMEI PRIVATE HIGH SCHOOL
This is so heavy!
[grunts] I did it!
[Hina] So she's the new badminton manager.
Gosh, it's seriously hot.
[Hina gasps]
How do you athletes handle this heat?
All right! [grunts]
[Hina whimpers]
I'm never gonna win.
[Niina] What? Win what exactly?
[Ayame] Fresh electrolytes, everybody!
[indistinct chatter]
Thank you, Manager!
- Oh, I feel alive again!
- [Ayame sighs]
Inota, what's next?
I'll show you the scorekeeping.
Aah! Yeah, let's see!
Um, listen.
It's a bit awkward to say this...
Oh?
But you tend to get really close to me.
I'd feel bad
if it caused rumors about you,
so it'd be great
if you could back off a little.
Wait, rumors?
Oh! You're the guy who played
Prince Charming in Snow White, right?
You just got it?
My friends were talking about it.
It must be weird hearing what people say.
Like speculating
about if you kissed or not.
Everyone's making
a big deal about some silly kiss.
[Taiki] Some silly... kiss?
Anyway, don't get too worked up about it.
Pay attention to the people in your life
who really care about you,
and you can just ignore everybody else.
[Taiki gasps softly]
Well, moving on from that,
I'd appreciate it if you'd scoot a bit.
Oops, my bad!
It's just a habit.
[exclaims, groans]
Spider!
[screams] It's a...
- a spider! It's a spider! [screams]
- Hey! What did I just say?
Yeah? I had no idea.
[Taiki gasps]
[Ayame] Inota!
Why aren't you doing anything?
- [Chinatsu] Oh! I forgot something!
- [Taiki yells]
This is not what it looks like!
[closing theme song playing]